Finding Aid for Michigan Union Records 1884-
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Michigan Union Board of Representatives 1980-1996, 1 linear feet
  The Michigan Union Board of Representatives records consist of minutes and related documentation covering the period 1980-1996. Minutes and supporting documents detail the reconfiguration of the board of representatives in the early 1980s as well as advisory information on Union policies and changing uses of the Union.
  - 1980-1996, 13 folders (Box 22)